Doraemon
It's good if it's so
If it can come to true it'll b nice
Different dreams
all can be arrived
The mysterious pocket
will compass it for you
I want to fly freely
Come on, use the dragonfly
Ah~Ah~Ah~ I love Doraemon most
(The Snail Room ls Very Relaxing)
I'll go home
Nobita
Yes!
What's up, mom
Come over
Yeah mom
What's the matter Mom
What did you test today
Calculation
Let me have a look
Yes
It's gone The paper disappeared
Nonsense
You don't want to let mom see it
and threw it away
No, I took it back
Show it to me then
Curious, where's it now
Mom hate those children who tell lies
I didn't tell a lie
What's the matter, Nobita
You did too much
You don't believe your child
I'm sad
Because you often told lie before
I don't believe you now
I'll leave home
I'll carry it out completely
Don't prevent me, Doraemon
I keep my promise Don't stop me
I didn't stop you
Mom said
we'd have delicious food tonight
and it's raining outside
You'll catch cold if you go out now
It's thundering!
Doraemon, do you have a way
to protest mom without leaving home
I've an idea
You can hide at home
instead of leaving home
Hide at home?
But I've one condition
What's it?
I'll get fifth six of the cake
You're too foxy
Or I won't help you
OK, I promise you
OK, wait and see
What's this
The snail room
Nobody can touch you
if you go inside it
I won't live in the small room
How do you feel
Er, Good
It's not narrow inside
I feel calm living in it
Before mom believes you
You'd stay here
Nobita, do you
know it's your mistake?
Where's Nobita?
He's here He's inside it
Mom will forgive you if you apologize
No~
What's your attitude?
You'll not be forgiven, come out
He can't hear anything when he's in it
OK I won't give you cake
I've an idea
Nobita, you broke the rules
Don't you forget the promise just now
Promise, promise
This is yours This is mine
Nobita How can you do like that
The one will win if he's quicker
Damn, Nobita
I won't lend the snail room to you
The cake is the most important now
Right It'd be so
Doraemon
Mom, buy more cake
No kidding
Don't play any more Go to study now
You won't become a great man
if you play all daylong
It's nice to watch the walkers
in breeze
Man
Nobita's wearing a snail shell
It's suitable to the clumsy Nobita
Big boob
Timid Nobita, come out
Damn, it's hateful
Shit I can't beat him today
Do you know it's powerful
The snail room is really good
I don't feel pain today
I like it
It's raining
Rain heavily
I'm not afraid of it
Morning, is Nobita in
He's in the snail room outside
Nobita, are you inside it
Hi Shizuka
Thank you for lending me the note
There's a paper in it
In it?
Thank you
Impossible
Then see you See you
Do you hear that?
I see OK, let's go home now
Great Nobita Go home now
No
I'm greatly hurt
Then... how will you forgive mom?
If you promise my request
I'll go out
Request?
Look at this one
Don't suspect of me
Don't force me to read
and increase the pocket money
Give me cake two times more a day
No way
And don't ask me to go out
to do anything
I won't wash face
when I feel it's troublesome
Right, let me have a look at the paper
The paper...
It's here
Nobita!
Your mark is too poor
Sorry~"
She's so angry, don't come out now
It's better if the paper isn't found
( Man-making Machine)
It's finished
It's completed just in two hours
I'll hang it on the wall
Hi, shall I help you
The boat made with Nobita's help
will sink, won't it?
Yeah
You look down upon me
We'll make a huge masterpiece
and let them have a look
OK
If we ask Doraemon's help
he'll bring out good things
Doraemon
You'd work hard to create
it's valuable
What's more
Don't touch the machine
in front of the table
What's that?
Don't ask, It's for others
I want to touch it after hearing that
I must touch it
What's this?
Man-making machine
You may create babies you like with it
What?
Is as the same as the real one
You may use the material beside you
The machine will take out
the structure as mankind
And rebuild them
I'll do that And let you have a look
Morning
I'm a salesman from the New World
Store, I come to reclaim the machine
No way, the owner isn't here now
It's troublesome...
Wait, I'll return it to you
Will please be quick
I see
OK, come to beat up the materials
One critter soap
one iron nail
100 match
450 pencils
and a cup of lime
and a pinch of sulfur and magnesium
and 1.8 litre water
It's enough to make a man
of 30gm weight
Soap, nail
ore, and broken sulfur
and match
The magnesium that grandpa
used to take photos
It's hard to get 450 pencils
Ask Shizuka to help
Shall we do it together?
Do what?
Baby
All my pocket is spent
to buy the pencils
Go ahead!
It begins to appear human shape
Let others have a look
It's painful
Sorry'
I... for I worry about the machine
Does anyone from the store come
to take it
Yes
Great
When I thought you'd play monkey trick
with it, I worry a lot
It's newly sales,
but it's found terrible bug later
And it's not allowed to be sold
The men made by the machine
named Niudan
They've super ability
Ordinary men aren't their opponents
They increase partners freely
They want to conquer mankind
And made terrible
turmoil in the future
and even the international turn out
What? You made?
Bad
It's too late...
Destroy the machine now
He's super ability, I can't defeat him
It's painful
Stop I'm your father
It seems someone is speaking
Bring the milk here
I see, He speaks to me with his sense
Nobita, sorry for just now
Because you made a curious joke
Whose milk is that?
My baby
It's not OK...
Golly...
No way, stop
Use the Reverse clock
Stop
Ah, Shizuka
I turn it to three o'clock ago
with the Reverse clock
What's up, they became
what they were three hours ago
(Steal Mom's Diamond)
Nobita
I'm coming
Put it where it was
Yes
Wait, what's that?
I found it in the corner
of the warehouse
It's the album of mom's childhood
I was lively before...
But it's terrible now
I miss...
Ah! This one!
I'm not willing to when I think of it
What's up?
This is your grandma who hug mom
Look at the finger
There's something shining
It's diamond
What a big diamond
It must be very expensive now
We can rebuild a home with it
And we can buy much paper money
to burn
Recorder Controlling plane
I can get what I like
How did you lose it, mom
It's not mom's mistake
I'll not forget it in my life
On July the 10th of
the year Zhaohe 23
Two suspectable men appeared...
They stole...
They stole the big diamond
they won't be forgiven
If I were there
I could drive them away
Let's drive them away
Right, we've time machine
OK, let's save it
Haha
Let's save it now
Go back to July the
10th of the year Zhaohe 23
The home where mom's born is near
Nobita, Nobita
It's as the same
as the it in the album
Follow her
What're you doing, boring
Mom's violent when she's young
and I couldn't not tell her the reason
It's troublesome...
But the diamonds really at that home
And the thief will appear
It's better
to monitor beside the diamond
Let's slide into it
Yuzi
How many times I repeat
till you'll understand
Put it down if you can't bring it out
You'd better tidy them up
What It's as the same as me
Where is the diamond?
It may in the garderobe
No
Is it here?
I found it
Look
Who're you
Mom There're strange men
I'll not forgive them if I find them
They must come here to steal this
Mom Is it diamond It's very expensive
isn't it?
Yeah
You'd give it to me when I grow up
OK
May I borrow it?
You do that again
Who want to play the marriage game,
come on
Swear in front of God now...
I've no method to deal with her
How can you look the diamond as a toy
But...
When will those two thief appear
It'll perform Move It's interesting
OK It'll begin
At that time the smile of the gold bat
came out from the treasure box
What'll we do with this?
Take it to our times
It's behavior of thief
Sorry
The child's troublesome
He didn't listen to me
Right, You may take this one
This is a valuable diamond
No, it's very cheap
It's made of glass
It can teach Yuzi a lesson
It'll adjust her character now
Did you lose the diamond?
Look for it till you find it
Who told you to put things freely
You're so poor...
It must be taken away by those two men
At that time
if there'd no such two thief...
It's better not tell her the truth now
Nobita, how come
you put the beg at the gate
To tell story while looking at the paper
Bride Game
It's strange
They two should not know
( Hot Powder)
Nobita, let's go to the swimming pool
to play
Let's go Nobita
Suneo's calling you
I see Boring
Nobita, let's go to the swimming pool
Will you go there?
Nobita can't swim
Nobita,
will you go to the swimming pool?
What's wrong with him?
I won't call him any more
Nobita, why do you escape everywhere
Hum Summer...
The tiresome season's coming
But they others ask you to swim
you're popular
They did that for I can't swim
In fact they don't want to swim
they want to see my bad performance
They look down upon me and laugh at me
You can practice there
I can't swim in the swimming pool
and it's crowded in the seashore
I won't learn to swim in my rest life
It's too strange
to let man imitate fish
Doraemon What're you doing
I put Hot Powder on you
I'll drawn
Take it away
It'll be like water around you
if you snap it
Can I practice swimming?
The flotage's bigger than water
any boob can swim
You can swim
as long as you master the key points
Can I really swim?
You may begin from fluttering water
Begin!
Make your knee straight
Ah, it plys No way
Don't be wordy Have a try
How dare you say that to me
I'll not lend you my swim ring
Swim!
Try the dog grabbling style
Look yourself as a dog Work hard
How can I do that
Ah? He's disappeared
Where's he?
Nobita, are you OK
Doraemon, it's too noisy
Madame What's the matter with you
I'm dazzling
He may go out
No
Where's he gone?
He's around Shizuka's
Let's visit her
Summer really arrives Work hard
Ladies
We almost get home
Dry your body up after you have a bath
We've got home
Ah! Nobita's tiresome!
Sorry Shizuka, you're surprised
It's not my mistake It's Nobita...
Lady-killer
I'm sorry
Where did Nobita run
Swim farther
I reach the lung
Go!
OK Rampart safely
Shit He asked me to go to the swim
in fact he wanted to play baseball
Suneo, do you know the result
after it's knocked out
Look, I'll play a swat
It's not so simple
I'll let you see how powerful I'm
Go!
Bingle Bingle
You're over
You destroy my chance to win
I'll beat you if I lose this time
How do you like it
Nobita's usually fooled by Suneo them
I've a chance to play with him
I'll beat him who makes mistakes
next time, do you know
It's Jian's turn next
Damn
Skyer
Come over
Jian's too clumsy Jian's rubbish
What're you saying
How dare you call my names
You said we could not mistake
Right
You'd remember yourself
Don't be wordy I get angry
Sorry Please forgive me
It's a little strange today
Doraemon
I know you were playing tricks just now
didn't you
No, it's not me
Stop Damn
Doraemon
Nobita, did you dive
with the Hot Powder
I come to revenge You wait
I... I only play a small trick
Suneo, snap the powder for me
OK
It's free Snap more
It's finished
OK I'm coming
Don't run!
I'm coming!
It's painful Why can't you swim
What's this
Is it the Hot Powder?
Bad No way
I won't give the real powder to you
We'll go home now
But I'm too tired and my hand
and feet can move
I want to go to the bank
But here's the land
Doraemon
Help me to get on the bank
Nobita!
It's hard to save
if one is snapped the powder
Nobita's good at making trouble
I can't look after it
(Shopping In The Future)
Did you see
I bought a new bicycle
it can be shifted gears for 8 times
Great Suneo
Cool Suneo
Thank you Shizuka, will you have a try
Really?
I've longing for it for a longtime
May I use it
Only a moment
You're really Suneo
This is the beeper
This is the gearbox
What a great bicycle
cool
Are you scared to ride it
No problem, it's a new one
and it's behavior's good
May I use it, Suneo
Nobita, Can you ride bicycle
I'll ask dad to buy me one
I hate the bicycle now
And I can't want to see anyone
I must buy one
Anyway, I want to buy one
I've used the mallet for ten years
I'll buy a now one
You can only say so
And my clothes is out of fashion too
It's shameful to take the mallet
to play golf
I'd lost face when I took part in
Nobita's Mather & Sister Day
But...
No way
There're many things
I want in the world
But I can't pay for it
I can't pay for it...
I'm sleepy
I'm very sleep)'
Doraemon
Are you there?
Is it the future Contents
There're many things in it
Furniture Fashion Books Bicycle
Bicycle
Page 50... Page 50...
It runs 50 ms in the first round
The highest speed is 200 kilometers
There's a road-keeping device
which prevent it from dashing
Great I want this one
This is...
As long as I say I want it
it'll come out...
OK Let's have a try
Golf article for use
The pushrod with mighty spring
And there's a golf inductive device
It's this one I want this sphere
Great
It's this one this time
I want this fashion
What's the matter?
Don't ask accept it
It's for your daily help
It's really the future bicycle
and I'll not fall
down when I sit on it
It's powerful
What's that wind just now
What?
How do you like my bicycle
The speed is 200 kms an hour
Where did you bought it?
You can get anything if you have this
You can book what you like
Dad takes the golf sphere
Mom takes the fashion
Shizuka takes the moppet
Jian takes the recorder
and Suneo takes the acoustics
Everyone is happy
Jian said he'd vocalize
with the recorder
Why did you do that
It's painful
Don't scare me
ls there anything I did wrong
You still ask me that
That's the mail ordered Contents
Will anyone come to collect the fee
When? How much?
You bought so many
It may take you 5 million yuan
It's the time to gather the money
Bad! I'll withdraw them!
They won't accept that
Then...
What'll they do if I can't afford it?
You'll be arrested as a swiz criminal
I take them
Tiresome Boring
Doraemon, I don't want take them
help me find a way
It's all because
you reckoned without your host
Even you adopt payment by installment
with your pocket...
It'll be 500 yuan a month...
You have to discuss it with father
No way
We do have a child named Nobita
He bought a bicycle
We have not a bicycle
Escape!
Don't run away
Nobita, hurry
Be quick
I've tried my best
We'll catch up with it be quicker
Huff)'
It's painful
Please pardon me Sorry
I'm really sorry
I'm terriblely sorry
To tell you the truth
the bicycle is newly put on sale
Our company found it's bug
we're now reclaim it
It'll disjoint itself if it runs
with high speed
It'll damage our reputation
if it's known to public
The other goods you bought is free
Please keep it as a secret
Free?
Why don't you help me buy some
But...
( The robot-control-training machine)
Nobita, I'll eat it
if you don't have it
OK
What's the matter with you
Why are you so excited
Bad! Nobita's bad habit begins again
Doraemon, I know you came again
Give me...
I'll announce first
Don't let me bring out the rocket
but you're the future...
Even it's in the future
It's still dangerous to travel in space
Some cosmonauts died
In the unlimited universe
There's no air
It's so hot that it can melt iron
And it's an extremely cold world
Universe Monster
The universe adventure team
won't accept you
who're lazy, timid, inconsiderate
and weak
Sorry, I said that too much, sorry
What's this?
The rocket-control-training machine
How to use it
Control it while sitting in the chair
you'll feel the adventure in space
The scene seen in the round disc
will become the scene in space
and reflect on the curtain
My room is reflected
Really
It seems that it's landing on some star
Set off
It's true, the scene's moving too
It comes near to the cliff
It'll knock on it
Avoid the wall
Turn left
Open the door
OK
There's a road between the cliffs
You're too foxy You only enjoy yourself
Let me play it OK
It's declivity
It's going downstairs
It's going round in a big U
It's too noisy I'll control myself
Bad
It's ice wall
What a pain
It seems it's going outside
It's too dangerous
I want to go out
Don't knock everywhere
if you want to go out
If the disc's cracked up
The device will bomb
I'll be careful
Increase the height
Those peaks'd be the roofs of our rooms
As if there's something on the roof
Come close to have a look
There's a monster
Run away
It's too excited
It's really like traveling in space
OK I'll be at treetop level
Great
Don't fly too fast
or you'll knock into something
No problem
It's spaceship
It'll know into it
It's dangerous
You'd be careful Nobita
You're too bold
It becomes black
We caught the flying object
Take it to the TV station
It's nice
to take it to the newspaper office
Or shall we take it as a pet?
Nobita and Doraemon
will be surprised
We fell into the singularity
Step on the gas
OK
Ah...?
What's up? Be quiet!
Ah...
Great We escaped
Ah?
There's a hole in that mountain
OK Let's go to have a look
Tiresome
There's a hole here
Come in it to have a look
What's the matter
Some accident happened
The disc doesn't work
I thought it was a strange bug
so I beat it down
What's this?
(Tatami )
I like rice cake most
I extremely like it
Delicious
I only had three
Me too
I want eat it!
What?
Doraemon, you're too foxy
Give it to me!
No, it's mine
I'll take it It's me who got it first
You two can't fight
What happened on earth
If there were another rice cake
we'd not quarrel
There's no rice cake here
You two like it so much
others will laugh at you
if you quarrel about it
If there're much rice cake
Right, we needn't to quarrel
I've an idea!
Oops? The rice cake-making machine?
There're no rice cake coming out
It's curious
I forgot to put materials into it
Mom
We want some rice
Don't play with rice
No, we'll make rice cake
No way
What a pity
It'll be no problem if we have material
OK, since it's so Let's plant rice
I can't wait so long
I've agricultural tools
This is the bottle to seal the seed
Is it?
The small sun
And the canned cloud
This is the scarecrow
and the field scroll
Fertilizer has been mixed into it
Don't be absent of mind, do me a favour
I see
Wow It's so cold
It's good
The harvest season's coming
in two hours
My waist is bitter
Don't you feel hot
Curious, it's far away from summer
It's not OK if there's no water
the rain is too less
There must be something wrong
with the season-controller
I'd not buy it if I know it earlier
The field is thirsty
It'll be over if you don't water it
Bad
The children have no sense of rules
They stepped on the floor
with dirty feet
There's some water
Mom May we use it
We're in great need of it
We don't worry now
The rain is too much this time
The paddy“ rot away
Stand here
It's OK
Move
Great it's fine now
Yeah
Look the spic comes out
ls there nit of locust on your tools?
Yeah It's true to nature
Yeah
We get good harvest
OK Let's reap it
It's happy to reap
Put the paddy into the machine
and it'll become rice
Then we can make
It comes out
The rice cake comes out
It seems nice
Delicious
It tastes great
How much can we make with that rice
It means...
Everyone of us will get 129
Ah There's another one less
Mine, it's mine I want 130
No I'm hard-working
(Cat runs a company)
It's should be OK
Nobita got up in the morning Sorry
I'll go to school
See you
Take care
It'll be good if he does so every day
I over slept Bad
I'll be quick to wash my face and teeth
and have meal
It's over I'll be late
Nobita,
Didn't you go to school on time
stop»-
Ah, I forgot
to take the time alert last night
I'll do it as planed
if I take it
Thank you for not letting me be late
Shizuka, what's the matter with you
you're upset in the morning
Do have anything worried
It's useless to tell you that
No, I'll do anything for you
Really Will you help me
I'm very glad
Thank you
It'll be over if mom finds it
I see
I heard it's thrown to Shizuka's
We've a dog and a canary
Mom doesn't let us feed it
As a man, I'd keep my promise
It goes smoothly
Mom
Don't cheat me
Mom doesn't allow me to go home
before I throw it away
Will uncle raise a cat?
I don't like it most
It's lovely
They're all for you, please accept them
I want to raise them, but I can't
because I live in the apartment
I hope some kind people will raise you
Don't come near! Cur!
It comes~
What'll I do on earth
It's too bad of the man
who gave the cat up
Where will I go?
The time alert runs
It's time to read books
Help me unchain it, I'll be scolded
Help me unchain it
No, it's troublesome
What're you doing
I've told him several times
Nobita!
He's reading in the snail room
Nobita, it's no use to hide, come out
OK, you wait to see
It's dangerous
What'll I do in the future
Doraemon, what'll we do
I'm a man too Let me have a try
It may succeed
What do you want to do
with four time alert
I'll do experiment
It'll be good if it succeeds
Doraemon, will it succeed
Have a little patience
Wait for another 5 minutes
5 minutes?
The kitty will stand up
Look Time is up
Open the door of the closet
It runs into it
According to the booked ceiling
When it's time book the computer
They'll go to the ceiling
to walk a beat
It begins
Succeeded
What's wrong with you?
I'm fearful of mouse
Mom, do you find
that mice are driven away by kitties
But you could not raise them at home
Still no way
It doesn't matter
that mom doesn't raise them
Why?
They don't need an owner now
they can build house and work
and live their life
It means they can sign contract
with several families
They'll go to the ceiling to
go their round regularly every day
What they earn will be paid
for the pet shop
The shop will send food to them regularly
I see
You'd let kitties
run a mouse-killing company
To establish a kitty com,.LTd
It's settled Go to find customers
OK~~
Great To run a kitty company?
I'll help you
Great Thank you
Please do more favour
Those cats work very hard
They did me great help
It goes well
It's rare that Doraemon
found such a good idea
Some faces are round
Some faces are long
Some faces are square
Some faces are triangular
Weeping Angry Fawning and requesting
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round